appdividend.com 2019-11-07

# Privacy Policy

### **Terms of use**

If you are using the [**AppDividend** ](http://appdividend.com/)website then you must accept this privacy policy. If not then please check out all the details of this website’s **Privacy Policy**. Otherwise, it is considered that you are accepting and you do not have any kind of objections against it.

### **Update  in Privacy Policy**

**Privacy Policy** of **AppDividend** is subject to change without any prior notice to visitors. **AppDividend  **can update this privacy **Privacy Policy** as and when required.

### **Data Sharing**

We don’t share your personal information with other or any external parties. We only collect the data to improve our service by collecting feedbacks of **our site**

If you find our article very useful or if you find any issues regarding our articles then you can contact us via comment section and for the comment, you need to give your name, email and website information to the  **AppDividend.**

Again, We don’t share your personal information with other or any external parties.

### **Cookies**

Cookies are created by your Web browser. We use cookies to enhance the user experience of **AppDividend**. We never place personally identifiable information in Cookies. Additionally, our business partners (for example, advertisers) may use cookies as well. **Our website** has no access or control of the advertiser’s web cookies and is not responsible for any information stored in these types of cookies. Visitors can disable the use of cookies by changing settings of their respective web browsers. However, if you disable Cookies, there might be chances that you can not access content on our Website effectively or at all.

### **Source code Copyrights**

All the contents and source code downloaded from this blog is the property of  **AppDividend** and can be used for personal education purpose only. Visitors are not allowed to use, copy or repost the source code to any business or commercial blogs. All the content **C** **opyrights** are held by  **AppDividend.**

### **Analytics &  Advertisement**

We are using the following tools to track user information and advertisement.

**Google Analytics:  **Track User Information.

### **We don’t collect**

**AppDividend  **does not collect information like contact number, credit/debit card details or other banking details from any visitor.

### **We collect**

**AppDividend  **collects personally identifiable information such as name, email address, and website.

### **Third-parties and Opt-Out**

Third-parties may display interest-based advertising to you in applications or websites, based on your use of applications or websites over time and across non-affiliated apps.

Such third parties may combine and use information from websites or applications on your current browser or device with information from your other browsers or devices for advertising purposes. 

To opt-out of such interest-based advertising and/or cross-device targeting, please use the methods provided below for opting out on each of your browsers and on each of your devices:

Network Advertising Initiative (NAI) – [**http://optout.networkadvertising.org/**](http://optout.networkadvertising.org/)  
Digital Advertising Alliance (DAA) – [**http://www.aboutads.info/choices/**](http://www.aboutads.info/choices/)  
Digital Advertising Alliance Canada (DAAC) – [**http://youradchoices.ca/choices**](http://youradchoices.ca/choices)  
Digital Advertising Alliance EU (EDAA) – [**http://www.youronlinechoices.com/**](http://www.youronlinechoices.com/)

Please note that opting out of interest-based advertising and cross-device targeting does not mean you will no longer receive online advertising. 

It does mean that the third-party from which you have opted out of receiving interest-based advertising or cross-device targeting by using the methods provided above will no longer deliver ads tailored to your Web preferences and usage patterns on a particular web browser or device.
